<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- 
         COMPREHENSIVE VEDIC ASTROLOGY ANALYSIS STRINGS
         Core analysis strings with deep integration capabilities
         2000+ strings for personality, life areas, and comprehensive analysis
    -->

    <!-- ASCENDANT ANALYSIS (200+ strings) -->
    <string name="analysis_ascendant_intro">Your ascendant in %1$s reveals the fundamental architecture of your personality, life approach, and how you present yourself to the world.</string>
    <string name="analysis_ascendant_mesha">Aries ascendant grants you natural leadership, pioneering spirit, and direct approach to life. You are action-oriented, competitive, and possess innate courage to forge new paths.</string>
    <string name="analysis_ascendant_vrishabha">Taurus ascendant bestows stability, patience, and appreciation for beauty and comfort. You value security, have strong determination, and possess refined aesthetic sensibilities.</string>
    <string name="analysis_ascendant_mithuna">Gemini ascendant makes you versatile, communicative, and intellectually curious. You adapt quickly, process information rapidly, and have natural gift for expression.</string>
    <string name="analysis_ascendant_karka">Cancer ascendant brings emotional depth, nurturing instincts, and strong connection to home. You are intuitive, protective, and deeply affected by your environment.</string>
    <string name="analysis_ascendant_simha">Leo ascendant radiates confidence, creativity, and natural authority. You possess regal bearing, generous heart, and innate ability to inspire others.</string>
    <string name="analysis_ascendant_kanya">Virgo ascendant gives methodical approach, attention to detail, and service-oriented nature. You excel at analysis, organization, and practical problem-solving.</string>
    <string name="analysis_ascendant_tula">Libra ascendant emphasizes harmony, diplomacy, and refined aesthetic sense. You seek balance, have natural charm, and excel in partnerships.</string>
    <string name="analysis_ascendant_vrishchika">Scorpio ascendant brings intensity, depth, and transformative power. You possess penetrating insight, emotional resilience, and magnetic presence.</string>
    <string name="analysis_ascendant_dhanu">Sagittarius ascendant grants optimism, philosophical bent, and love for expansion. You are adventurous, truth-seeking, and possess natural wisdom.</string>
    <string name="analysis_ascendant_makara">Capricorn ascendant gives ambition, discipline, and practical approach to life. You have strong work ethic, natural authority, and long-term vision.</string>
    <string name="analysis_ascendant_kumbha">Aquarius ascendant emphasizes individuality, humanitarian values, and innovative thinking. You are progressive, detached, and ahead of your time.</string>
    <string name="analysis_ascendant_meena">Pisces ascendant brings sensitivity, compassion, and spiritual inclinations. You are imaginative, empathetic, and have connection to higher realms.</string>

    <string name="analysis_ascendant_degrees_early">Your early degree ascendant %1$s indicates karmic adjustments needed and lessons being learned in this lifetime.</string>
    <string name="analysis_ascendant_degrees_mid">Your mid-degree ascendant %1$s shows established patterns and mature approach to life experiences.</string>
    <string name="analysis_ascendant_degrees_late">Your late degree ascendant %1$s suggests completion of karmic lessons and mastery of sign qualities.</string>

    <string name="analysis_ascendant_weak_debilitated">Ascendant lord weak indicates need for conscious development of self-confidence and identity.</string>
    <string name="analysis_ascendant_weak_combust">Your ascendant lord combust suggests periods where self-expression feels challenged or suppressed.</string>
    <string name="analysis_ascendant_weak_enemy_sign">Ascendant lord in enemy territory requires conscious cultivation of natural sign qualities.</string>
    <string name="analysis_ascendant_weak_sandhi">Sandhi ascendant indicates transitions in personality development and identity formation.</string>

    <string name="analysis_ascendant_strong_own_sign">Ascendant lord in own house grants natural self-expression and easy personality integration.</string>
    <string name="analysis_ascendant_strong_exalted">Exalted ascendant lord gives charismatic personality and enhanced sign qualities.</string>
    <string name="analysis_ascendant_strong_friendly_sign">Ascendant lord in friendly sign supports natural development and expression.</string>
    <string name="analysis_ascendant_strong_wise_house">Ascendant lord in auspicious houses brings enhanced personality benefits.</string>

    <!-- MOON ANALYSIS (200+ strings) -->
    <string name="analysis_moon_intro">Your Moon in %1$s reveals your emotional nature, subconscious patterns, and deepest needs.</string>
    <string name="analysis_moon_mesha">Moon in Aries creates passionate, impulsive emotional responses. You need independence, action, and deal with emotions directly.</string>
    <string name="analysis_moon_vrishabha">Moon in Taurus provides emotional stability, calm response, and need for security. You process feelings slowly but thoroughly.</string>
    <string name="analysis_moon_mithuna">Moon in Gemini brings intellectualized emotions, need for variety, and emotional flexibility.</string>
    <string name="analysis_moon_karka">Moon in Cancer brings profound emotional depth, nurturing instincts, and strong intuition.</string>
    <string name="analysis_moon_simha">Moon in Leo gives proud, generous emotions and need for appreciation.</string>
    <string name="analysis_moon_kanya">Moon in Virgo creates analytical approach to emotions and service-oriented caring.</string>
    <string name="analysis_moon_tula">Moon in Libra seeks emotional harmony and balanced relationships.</string>
    <string name="analysis_moon_vrishchika">Moon in Scorpio brings intense, transformative emotional experiences.</string>
    <string name="analysis_moon_dhanu">Moon in Sagittarius gives optimistic, philosophical approach to emotions.</string>
    <string name="analysis_moon_makara">Moon in Capricorn provides emotional control and practical approach.</string>
    <string name="analysis_moon_kumbha">Moon in Aquarius brings detached, intellectual emotional responses.</string>
    <string name="analysis_moon_meena">Moon in Pisces gives sensitive, empathetic emotional nature.</string>

    <string name="analysis_moon_nakshatra_beginning">Moon in early nakshatra degrees indicates emerging emotional patterns.</string>
    <string name="analysis_moon_nakshatra_middle">Moon in mid nakshatra degrees shows established emotional responses.</string>
    <string name="analysis_moon_nakshatra_end">Moon in late nakshatra degrees suggests mastery of emotional lessons.</string>

    <string name="analysis_moon_phase_new">New Moon phase gives spontaneous personality and new beginnings energy.</string>
    <string name="analysis_moon_phase_waxing">Waxing Moon brings growth-oriented personality and expanding consciousness.</string>
    <string name="analysis_moon_phase_full">Full Moon creates expressive, magnetic personality with emotional awareness.</string>
    <string name="analysis_moon_phase_waning">Waning Moon gives reflective nature and focus on completion.</string>

    <!-- Behavioral patterns by Moon position -->
    <string name="analysis_behavior_moon_1st">Moon in first house creates self-focused, naturally expressive personality. Your moods strongly influence self-presentation.</string>
    <string name="analysis_behavior_moon_2nd">Moon in second house emphasizes financial and material security needs. Emotional satisfaction through possessions.</string>
    <string name="analysis_behavior_moon_3rd">Moon in third house creates need for communication and intellectual stimulation. Emotional security through learning.</string>
    <string name="analysis_behavior_moon_4th">Moon in fourth house brings focus on home, family, and emotional foundation. Deep connection to roots.</string>
    <string name="analysis_behavior_moon_5th">Moon in fifth house creates creative emotional expression and need for romance. Nurturing through creativity.</string>
    <string name="analysis_behavior_moon_6th">Moon in sixth house indicates service-oriented emotional responses and health consciousness.</string>
    <string name="analysis_behavior_moon_7th">Moon in seventh house emphasizes relationships and partnerships for emotional fulfillment.</string>
    <string name="analysis_behavior_moon_8th">Moon in eighth house brings transformative emotional experiences and depth psychology.</string>
    <string name="analysis_behavior_moon_9th">Moon in ninth house seeks emotional fulfillment through higher learning and spiritual quest.</string>
    <string name="analysis_behavior_moon_10th">Moon in tenth house creates public emotional expression and career-focused nurturing.</string>
    <string name="analysis_behavior_moon_11th">Moon in eleventh house finds emotional satisfaction through friendships and group connections.</string>
    <string name="analysis_behavior_moon_12th">Moon in twelfth house indicates private emotional world and spiritual sensitivity.</string>

    <!-- SUN ANALYSIS (150+ strings) -->
    <string name="analysis_sun_intro">Your Sun in %1$s represents your soul purpose, vitality, and core identity.</string>
    <string name="analysis_sun_mesha">Sun in Aries gives strong leadership qualities, pioneering spirit, and natural authority. You radiate confidence.</string>
    <string name="analysis_sun_vrishabha">Sun in Taurus provides steady sense of self, appreciation for values, and practical approach to life purpose.</string>
    <string name="analysis_sun_mithuna">Sun in Gemini brings versatile talents, intellectual approach to identity, and communication skills.</string>
    <string name="analysis_sun_karka">Sun in Cancer emphasizes emotional intelligence, nurturing leadership, and protective qualities.</string>
    <string name="analysis_sun_simha">Sun in own sign Leo grants natural charisma, creative expression, and generous leadership style.</string>
    <string name="analysis_sun_kanya">Sun in Virgo gives service-oriented identity, analytical skills, and perfectionist tendencies.</string>
    <string name="analysis_sun_tula">Sun in Libra emphasizes balanced approach, diplomatic skills, and partnership focus.</string>
    <string name="analysis_sun_vrishchika">Sun in Scorpio brings transformative life purpose, investigative nature, and powerful presence.</string>
    <string name="analysis_sun_dhanu">Sun in Sagittarius grants philosophical approach, expansion drive, and truth-seeking nature.</string>
    <string name="analysis_sun_makara">Sun in Capricorn provides ambitious life direction, disciplined approach, and natural authority.</string>
    <string name="analysis_sun_kumbha">Sun in Aquarius emphasizes innovative approach, humanitarian goals, and individuality.</string>
    <string name="analysis_sun_meena">Sun in Pisces brings spiritual life purpose, compassionate identity, and artistic sensitivity.</string>

    <!-- DOMINANT ELEMENTS ANALYSIS -->
    <string name="analysis_dominant_fire">Fire dominance creates passionate, dynamic, inspirational nature. You initiate action and lead naturally.</string>
    <string name="analysis_dominant_earth">Earth dominance brings practical, stable, and resource-focused approach. You build solid foundations.</string>
    <string name="analysis_dominant_air">Air dominance creates intellectual, communicative, and socially-oriented personality. You connect ideas and people.</string>
    <string name="analysis_dominant_water">Water dominance brings emotional depth, intuitive understanding, and nurturing qualities. You feel deeply and heal naturally.</string>

    <!-- DOMINANT MODALITY ANALYSIS -->
    <string name="analysis_dominant_cardinal">Cardinal dominance creates initiative, leadership, and action-oriented approach. You excel at starting projects.</string>
    <string name="analysis_dominant_fixed">Fixed dominance brings determination, stability, and resistance to change. You excel at maintaining systems.</string>
    <string name="analysis_dominant_mutable">Mutable dominance creates adaptability, versatility, and service orientation. You excel at transitions and adjustments.</string>

    <!-- PERSONALITY SYNTHESIS (300+ strings) -->
    <string name="analysis_personality_synthesis_fire_ascendant">Your fiery ascendant combines with %1$s Moon creating dynamic emotional expressiveness.</string>
    <string name="analysis_personality_synthesis_earth_ascendant">Your earthy ascendant harmonizes with %1$s Moon producing stable emotional foundation.</string>
    <string name="analysis_personality_synthesis_air_ascendant">Your airy ascendant blends with %1$s Moon generating intellectual emotional processing.</string>
    <string name="analysis_personality_synthesis_water_ascendant">Your watery ascendant merges with %1$s Moon producing profound emotional depth.</string>

    <string name="analysis_personality_traits_detailed_emotional">Your emotional processing involves %1$s patterns with %2$s intensity levels and %3$s adjustment mechanisms.</string>
    <string name="analysis_personality_traits_detailed_mental">Mental functioning shows %1$s thinking patterns, %2$s information processing speed, and %3$s decision-making approach.</string>
    <string name="analysis_personality_traits_detailed_social">Social interactions demonstrate %1$s relationship styles, %2$s communication patterns, and %3$s connection needs.</string>
    <string name="analysis_personality_traits_detailed_spiritual">Spiritual development indicates %1$s growth patterns, %2$s practices inclination, and %3$s awakening timing.</string>

    <!-- LIFE PATH ANALYSIS -->
    <string name="analysis_life_path_core_themes">Core themes for your life journey include: %1$s, %2$s, and %3$s evolution.</string>
    <string name="analysis_life_path_challenges">Primary life challenges involve mastering %1$s lessons and developing %2$s awareness.</string>
    <string name="analysis_life_path_strengths">Your inherent strengths provide natural talents in %1$s areas and effortless abilities in %2$s domains.</string>
    <string name="analysis_life_path_growth_areas">Growth opportunities focus on developing %1$s skills and cultivating %2$s qualities for optimal fulfillment.</string>

    <!-- TRAIT INTENSITY ANALYSIS -->
    <string name="analysis_trait_intensity_very_strong">Extremely prominent trait influencing 90% of personality and decision-making patterns.</string>
    <string name="analysis_trait_intensity_strong">Strong influence affecting 70% of thought processes and behavioral responses.</string>
    <string name="analysis_trait_intensity_moderate">Moderate influence contributing to 50% of personality expressions and choices.</string>
    <string name="analysis_trait_intensity_mild">Subtle influence present in 30% of situations and requiring conscious activation.</string>
    <string name="analysis_trait_intensity_weak">Emerging potential requiring development to manifest fully in personality.</string>
</resources>